<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on </title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty WaW Zombie mod hack</title>
      <link>/projects/codwaw_hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/codwaw_hack/</guid>
      <description>Call of Duty&amp;rsquo;s Zombie Mod stands as an adrenaline-packed action and daunting challenge. This game mode puts players through a test of endurance. However, sometimes, the thrill of the game can morph into frustration as the difficulty spikes. It&amp;rsquo;s at times like these that a touch of ingenuity can alter the table&amp;rsquo;s turn. As a seasoned player and a passionate hacker, I believe in tilting the scales a bit towards our favor every once in a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KarolaScript</title>
      <link>/projects/karolascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/karolascript/</guid>
      <description>In my quest to better comprehend the fascinating intricacies of compilation process, compiler, and interpreter knowledge, I embarked on a journey of creating my own programming language - KarolaScript.
KarolaScript is a decidely bare-bones, yet enlightening endeavor, which brings the underpinnings of a language interpreter to the foreground. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t boast rich features like an interactive debugger or a sophisticated static analyzer, as its primary purpose is to serve as a learning playground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minesweeper Hack</title>
      <link>/projects/minesweeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/minesweeper/</guid>
      <description>This game is small enough not to be overwhelming, yet complex enough to make it a fun challenge. While there are definitely easier ways to crack this code, I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen a learn-as-I-go approach which might not be the quickest, but undoubtedly helps me delve deeper into the essence of reverse engineering.
 Imported Libraries Since minesweeper is a GUI application, it uses graphics function which prints those graphics to the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DirDigger</title>
      <link>/projects/dirdigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/dirdigger/</guid>
      <description>About project DirDigger is an efficient directory digging and busting tool that offers a range of features surpassing those of its alternatives. It serves a dual purpose, being an invaluable asset for both CTF enthusiasts and individuals engaged in the scanning of web app directories and API URLs encompassing bug bounty programs.
Originally conceived as a portfolio project to create a Burp extension similar to gobuster/dirbuster, DirDigger experienced the creation and implementation of novel ideas and features, transforming it into a fully comprehensive directory digging tool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>