<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Minesweeper Hack</title>
      <link>/projects/minesweeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/minesweeper/</guid>
      <description>This game is small enough not to be overwhelming, yet complex enough to make it a fun challenge. While there are definitely easier ways to crack this code, I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen a learn-as-I-go approach which might not be the quickest, but undoubtedly helps me delve deeper into the essence of reverse engineering.
 Imported Libraries Since minesweeper is a GUI application, it uses graphics function which prints those graphics to the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome, hackerspace explorers! This blog serves as the digital log on my journey towards becoming skillful in security research. The material you&amp;rsquo;ll discover here reflects the progression of my journey and my passion for growing my skills.
I am on a committed pursuit to establish a career in cybersecurity, with a special emphasis on 0-day vulnerability research. My current main interests are reverse engineering, browsers, exploit dev, virtualization, iOS and malware, and as I explore these domains and uncover their intricacies, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing invaluable insights and experiences right here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DirDigger</title>
      <link>/projects/dirdigger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/dirdigger/</guid>
      <description>About project DirDigger is an efficient directory digging and busting tool that offers a range of features surpassing those of its alternatives. It serves a dual purpose, being an invaluable asset for both CTF enthusiasts and individuals engaged in the scanning of web app directories and API URLs encompassing bug bounty programs.
Originally conceived as a portfolio project to create a Burp extension similar to gobuster/dirbuster, DirDigger experienced the creation and implementation of novel ideas and features, transforming it into a fully comprehensive directory digging tool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>