<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reverse engineering on </title>
    <link>/tags/reverse-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reverse engineering on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/reverse-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty WaW Zombie mod hack</title>
      <link>/projects/codwaw_hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/codwaw_hack/</guid>
      <description>Call of Duty&amp;rsquo;s Zombie Mod stands as an adrenaline-packed action and daunting challenge. This game mode puts players through a test of endurance. However, sometimes, the thrill of the game can morph into frustration as the difficulty spikes. It&amp;rsquo;s at times like these that a touch of ingenuity can alter the table&amp;rsquo;s turn. As a seasoned player and a passionate hacker, I believe in tilting the scales a bit towards our favor every once in a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compilers Introduction</title>
      <link>/posts/compilerintro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/compilerintro/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever found yourself intrigued by the complex science behind how exactly your written code transforms into an understandable stream of zeroes and ones, then you&amp;rsquo;re in exactly the right place. The realm of computer science goes far beyond just writing lines of code — at its core, it is about facilitating communication between humans and machines. This blog post pulls back the curtain on one such essential tool that makes this interaction possible: compilers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minesweeper Hack</title>
      <link>/projects/minesweeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/minesweeper/</guid>
      <description>This game is small enough not to be overwhelming, yet complex enough to make it a fun challenge. While there are definitely easier ways to crack this code, I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen a learn-as-I-go approach which might not be the quickest, but undoubtedly helps me delve deeper into the essence of reverse engineering.
 Imported Libraries Since minesweeper is a GUI application, it uses graphics function which prints those graphics to the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>